# GISELE LIMA

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

## SUMMARY

I am a Junior Web Developer with plenty of enthusiasm to start applying my full-stack technical knowledge into creative solutions that can help customers to thrive.

My background includes 13 years of experience working as Production Engineer and Leader of Continuous Improvement Projects.

## KEY PROJECTS

### **VEGME APP**

## https://vegme-app.herokuapp.com/

- Two-sided marketplace application utilising user authentication and authorisation
- Users are customers looking for delivery of vegan meals and restaurants offering their meal options to that niche market
- Features: CRUD functionalities, image handling via CDN, shopping cart and payment gateway
- Built with Ruby on Rails, PostgreSQL and Cloudinary

### ALTERNATIVE PAYROLL APP

## https://github.com/limagisele/terminal-app.git

- Ruby terminal app created from the need to implement a backup software where employees can enter their timesheets and managers can generate payroll reports while main system is down
- Features: users sign-in, timecard management through CRUD actions, report generated as csv file
- Developed using TDD cycle

## **PORTFOLIO WEBSITE**

## https://giselelima.netlify.app/

- Static website built to apply HTML and CSS knowledge while creating a portfolio to display projects developed during bootcamp
- Key focus was to implement a responsive and mobile-first design with Flexbox



0478 961 861



limagisele05@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/limagisele



github.com/limagisele



Bonbeach, Vic 3196

## EDUCATION

2022 - DIPLOMA OF IT

Coder Academy

## 2014 - MASTERS IN PRODUCTION MANAGEMENT

Universidade Federal de Pernambuco

# 2008 - BACHELOR IN PRODUCTION ENGINEERING

Universidade Federal de Pernambuco

## SKILLS

- Agile Methodology
- Troubleshooting / Debugging
- Project Management
- Adaptability
- Analytical Thinking
- Languages: HTML, CSS, Sass, Ruby,
   JavaScript, React.js, Node.js
- Framework: Rails, Bootstrap,
   Express
- Version Control: Git, GitHub
- Database: PostgreSQL, MongoDB
- Deployment: Heroku, Netlify
- Unit Testing: Jest, RSpec

# GISELE LIMA JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

## PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT

### PRODCUTION MANAGER

Coca-Cola Europacific Partners

### 2021 - 2022

- Managed team of 3 team managers, 1 scheduler and 23 operators
- Visited critical customer's warehouse to analyse recurrent packaging complaints, then implemented improvement plan which reduced this type of complaint to zero and increased customer's satisfaction
- Improved department's Quality KPIs by 25%, through development of team's ownership and commitment with the quality standards of their lines

### **LINE MANAGER**

Nestle

#### 2016 - 2021

- Identified business improvement opportunities to achieve
   Business Plan targets and presented them to key stakeholders for approval prior to implementation
- Led improvement project consulting user's needs and feedbacks, that resulted in 38% increase of production line's output and saving of \$113k/year in material cost
- Developed and implemented training plan to transfer tech skills from one site to another, allowing site to meet the deadlines of shutting down original site and starting up the new one on-time

## **CONTINUOUS IMPROVEMENT COORDINATOR**

Brose Group (Fiat-Chrysler Jeep Automobiles Supplier Park) **2015 - 2015** 

- Drove the internal cultural change while adapting Brose's system to Fiat's (client) requirements
- Implemented Management System for a brand-new site, which was classified by client's ranking as benchmarking for other suppliers

## CERTIFICATION

### JAVASCRIPT DEVELOPMENT

General Assembly (In Progress)

## LEAN SIX SIGMA GREEN BELT

Melbourne University **2019** 

## VOLUNTEERING

### **VOLUNTEER TUTOR**

Melbourne AMEP

May 2021 - Current

- Support recent migrants to settle in Australia
- Practice job interviews with students preparing for employment